Power Patron vs.
Dark Magician.
Game 1.
Power Patron goes first.
Dark Magician discards Mulcharmy Purulia. so Dark Magician draws whenever Power Patron Normal or Special Summons
from the hand this turn.
Power Patron Normal Summons Medius the Pure.
Dark Magician draws Dark Magician.
Power Patron activates Medius. then Special Summons Nervedo the Shadebeast Power Patron.
Power Patron places Jupredo the Shademachine Power Patron in the Pendulum Zone.
Jupredo's effect destroys Nervedo.
Jupredo destroys itself.
Power Patron uses Jupredo's face-up Extra Deck effect. then uses Nervedo's face-up Extra Deck effect. then
Special Summons Power Patron DoomZ.
Power Patron adds Prohibited Power Patron Portal - Terminus from the Deck.
Power Patron activates DoomZ. then Xyz Summons DoomZ Break - Diactorus using Medius as material. then
DoomZ equips to Diactorus.
Power Patron activates Terminus. then sends Purification Power Patron from the Extra Deck to the Graveyard.
then adds Medius from the Deck.
Power Patron places Shade the Obscure in the Pendulum Zone.
The destroyed Xyz Monster's material Medius goes to the Graveyard.
Power Patron Xyz Summons DoomZ XIII Over - Graflareio using Medius and Diactorus as material.
Power Patron activates DoomZ. then adds Jupredo from the Deck.
Power Patron places Jupredo in the Pendulum Zone.
Power Patron Special Summons Nervedo.
Power Patron's Shade triggers after a low-ATK monster is Special Summoned.
Power Patron returns Shade to the hand.
Power Patron activates Nervedo. then banishes the top 3 cards of the Deck face-down.
Nervedo destroys itself.
Power Patron Fusion Summons Nerva the Power Patron of Creation.
Power Patron activates Shade. then Special Summons Shade.
Dark Magician draws Magician's Rod.
Power Patron activates Shade. then pays 1000 Life Points. then returns Jupredo to the Extra Deck.
Power Patron returns Vidolium the Unstable Power Patron of Unity to the Extra Deck.
Power Patron uses Vidolium's face-up Extra Deck effect. then adds Vidolium from the Deck.
Power Patron places Vidolium in the Pendulum Zone.
Vidolium's effect destroys it and gives original Level 12 Power Patron monsters 5000 ATK for the
rest of the turn.
Power Patron activates Graflareio. then detaches Diactorus as material. then adds DoomZ Destruction from the Deck.
Power Patron sets Destruction.
Draw for turn.
Dark Magician activates Dark Magician. the Pharaoh's Servant.
Soul Servant becomes the next Chain Link. followed by Dark Magical Curtain.
Dark Magician Special Summons Dark Magician. the Pharaoh's Servant.
Destruction equips to Graflareio.
Dark Magician Special Summons Dark Magician. the Pharaoh's Servant. then sets The Gaze of Timaeus.
Dark Magician banishes Dark Magician. the Pharaoh's Servant. then Special Summons Dark Magician of Destruction.
Dark Magician activates Soul Servant. then banishes Soul Servant. then draws Infinite Impermanence.
Dark Magician Fusion Summons Magistus Chorozo.
Dark Magician Normal Summons the Rod.
Dark Magician Link Summons S:P Little Knight using the Rod and Magistus Chorozo as material. then
sets Infinite Impermanence.
Dark Magician's S:P attacks and destroys Shade.
Draw for turn.
Power Patron Normal Summons Medius.
Power Patron activates Medius.
Dark Magician chains S:P in response. then banishes Nerva. then banishes S:P.
Power Patron Special Summons Nervedo.
Dark Magician activates Infinite Impermanence.
Power Patron activates DoomZ. then Xyz Summons Jupiter the Power Patron of Destruction using Nervedo as
material. then DoomZ equips to Jupiter.
Power Patron activates Jupiter. then detaches Nervedo as material. then Special Summons Diactorus.
Power Patron activates Diactorus.
Diactorus destroys Graflareio.
Diactorus destroys Destruction.
Graflareio's material Medius goes to the Graveyard.
Power Patron sets Dominus Impulse.
Power Patron's Jupiter attacks directly for 3500 damage.
Power Patron's Diactorus attacks directly for 2400 damage.
Power Patron's Medius attacks directly for 1800 damage.
Power Patron Link Summons S:P using Diactorus and Medius as material.
Power Patron activates S:P. then banishes Dark Magician. the Pharaoh's Servant.
Dark Magician activates Timaeus. then returns the Magician to the Extra Deck. then Fusion Summons Red-Eyes Dark Dragoon.
Dark Magician activates the Rod. then sends Dragoon to the Graveyard. then recovers the Rod from the Graveyard.
Power Patron puts Nerva on the field.
Dark Magician puts S:P on the field.
Draw for turn.
Dark Magician Normal Summons the Rod.
Dark Magician activates the Rod.
Power Patron chains S:P in response.
Dark Magician chains S:P in response. then banishes S:P. then banishes Nerva.
Power Patron banishes the Rod.
Dark Magician adds Soul Servant from the Deck.
Dark Magician activates Soul Servant.
Dark Magician activates Illusion of Chaos. then adds the Rod from the Deck. then returns Dark
Magician to the Deck.
Dark Magician puts S:P on the field.
Power Patron puts Nerva on the field.
Dark Magician puts the Rod on the field.
Draw for turn.
Power Patron's Jupiter attacks the Rod. destroys it. and deals 1900 damage.
Power Patron wins the duel.
Power Patron wins Game 1.
Power Patron vs.
Dark Magician.
Game 2.
Dark Magician goes first.
Dark Magician activates Dark Magician. the Pharaoh's Servant. then Special Summons Dark Magician. the Pharaoh's Servant.
then sets The Gaze of Timaeus.
Dark Magician activates Dark Magical Circle. then adds Timaeus from the Deck.
Dark Magician activates Timaeus.
Power Patron chains Droll & Lock Bird in response. preventing either player from adding more cards
from the Main Deck to the hand for the rest of the turn.
Dark Magician returns Dark Magician. the Pharaoh's Servant to the Deck. then Fusion Summons Red-Eyes Dark Dragoon.
Dark Magician sets The Fallen & The Virtuous.
Draw for turn.
Power Patron Normal Summons Medius the Pure.
Power Patron activates Medius to add or Special Summon a Power Patron from the Deck.
Dark Magician chains Dragoon in response. then sends Illusion of Chaos from the hand to the Graveyard.
Medius's effect is negated.
Dark Magician sends Medius to the Graveyard.
Power Patron activates Prohibited Power Patron Portal - Terminus. then sends Purification Power Patron from the
Extra Deck to the Graveyard. then adds Medius from the Deck.
Power Patron activates Medius in the Graveyard. then returns Medius to the Deck. then Special Summons Medius.
Dark Magician activates Fallen & Virtuous. then sends Albion the Branded Dragon from the Extra Deck
to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Medius; Medius is banished instead of going to the Graveyard.
Power Patron places Junoldo the Shadespirit Power Patron in the Pendulum Zone.
Power Patron places Jupredo the Shademachine Power Patron in the Pendulum Zone.
Power Patron sets Typhoon.
Dark Magician banishes Dragoon. then activates Albion the Branded Dragon. then sets Fallen & Virtuous.
Draw for turn.
Dark Magician activates Soul Servant.
Dark Magician activates Fallen & Virtuous. then sends Ecclesia and the Dark Dragon from the Extra
Deck to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Junoldo the Shadespirit Power Patron.
Power Patron activates Junoldo the Shadespirit Power Patron. then recovers Terminus from the Graveyard.
Dark Magician activates Ecclesia and the Dark Dragon. then returns Ecclesia and the Dark Dragon to
the Extra Deck. then returns Albion the Branded Dragon to the Extra Deck.
Dark Magician returns Jupredo to the Deck.
Draw for turn.
Power Patron activates Terminus. then sends Nervedo the Shadebeast Power Patron from the Deck to the
Graveyard. then adds Medius from the Deck.
Power Patron Normal Summons Medius.
Power Patron activates Medius.
Dark Magician chains Fallen & Virtuous in response. then sends Albion the Branded Dragon from the
Extra Deck to the Graveyard.
Power Patron chains Duality in response. then Synchro Summons Herald of the Arc Light. then Special Summons Nervedo.
Power Patron activates Nervedo. then banishes the top 3 cards of the Deck face-down.
Nervedo destroys itself.
Power Patron Fusion Summons Nerva the Power Patron of Creation.
Power Patron uses Nervedo's face-up Extra Deck effect. then Special Summons Power Patron DoomZ.
Power Patron activates DoomZ. then Xyz Summons DoomZ Break - Diactorus using Herald of the Arc
Light as material. then DoomZ equips to Diactorus.
Power Patron activates Diactorus.
Diactorus destroys DoomZ.
Power Patron activates DoomZ. then adds Jupredo from the Deck.
Power Patron activates Medius in the Graveyard. then returns Jupredo to the Deck. then Special Summons Medius.
Power Patron activates Typhoon. then sends Dark Magical Circle to the Graveyard.
The destroyed Xyz Monster's material Herald of the Arc Light goes to the Graveyard.
Power Patron Xyz Summons DoomZ XIII Over - Graflareio using Herald of the Arc Light and
Diactorus as material.
Power Patron activates Graflareio. then detaches Herald of the Arc Light as material. then adds DoomZ
Destruction from the Deck.
Power Patron sends Timaeus to the Graveyard.
Power Patron sets Destruction.
Power Patron's Nerva attacks directly for 3300 damage.
Power Patron activates Duality. then banishes Duality. then returns Herald of the Arc Light to the Extra Deck.
Power Patron returns Purification to the Extra Deck.
Graflareio's material Diactorus goes to the Graveyard.
Power Patron Link Summons Purification using Nerva and Graflareio as material.
Power Patron activates Purification.
Power Patron banishes Medius. then Link Summons S:P Little Knight using Purification as material.
Power Patron activates S:P. then banishes Illusion of Chaos.
Draw for turn.
Power Patron activates Plundered Power Patron Plane - Vidolia.
Vidolia's effect banishes one card from the hand face-down to Special Summon Nervedo from the Deck.
Power Patron activates Jupredo. then banishes the top 3 cards of the Deck face-down.
Jupredo destroys itself.
Power Patron Xyz Summons Jupiter the Power Patron of Destruction.
Power Patron uses Jupredo's face-up Extra Deck effect. then adds Terminus from the Deck.
Power Patron's Jupiter attacks directly for 3500 damage.
Power Patron's S:P attacks directly for 1600 damage.
Power Patron wins the duel.
Power Patron wins Game 2.
Final score: Power Patron 2–0.